(Leonard:)How'd you get
ready so fast?
(Penny:)Oh, I pack light.
(Penny:)Once, I got through
an entire spring break
(Penny:)with nothing
but a long T-shirt and a belt.
(Leonard:)Why did you need a belt?
(Penny:)It's called an
evening look.
(Penny:)I've never been to
New Jersey before.
(Leonard:)It gets a bad rap from shows
like Jersey Shore
and Real Housewives.
(Penny:)So it's not
really like that?
(Leonard:)No, it's like that.
(Leonard:)Well, I'm excited
to show you around.
(Penny:)You think we'll have time
to visit your mom over there?
(Leonard:)Yes. We'll also have time to put
my junk in a garlic press,
(Leonard:)but I'm not
doing that either.
(phone chimes)
(Leonard:)Uh-oh.
(Leonard:)I just got an alert.
(Leonard:)Our flight's
been canceled.
(Penny:)What?
(Leonard:)Yeah, looks like
there's a big storm
(Leonard:)all up the East Coast.
(Penny:)Well, can we get
on another airline?
(Leonard:)I don't think so.
(Penny:)So, that's it?
(Penny:)We're not going?
(Leonard:)I guess not.
(scoffs)
(Penny:)Well, that sucks.
(Penny:)Yeah.